{
  "topic_id":"205",
  "questions": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "How many different types of paragraphs are in an essay?",
      "choice": ["One", "Two", "Three", "Four"],
      "answer": 2,
      "explanation": "",
      "keywords": []
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "What do you call the first paragraph in a formal essay?",
      "choice": ["Beginning", "Grabber", "Hook", "Introduction"],
      "answer": 3,
      "explanation": "",
      "keywords": []
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "What do you call the last paragraph in a formal essay?",
      "choice": ["Resolution", "Conclusion", "Ending", "Finale"],
      "answer": 1,
      "explanation": "",
      "keywords": []
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "question": "Begin every body paragraph with  _________________.",
      "choice": [
        "a lead",
        "an introduction",
        "a topic sentence",
        "background information"
      ],
      "answer": 2,
      "explanation": "",
      "keywords": []
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "question": "Which transition signals a conclusion?",
      "choice": ["In addition,", "Similarly,", "For example,", "In short,"],
      "answer": 3,
      "explanation": "",
      "keywords": []
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "question": "All of the following are acceptable types of hooks when writing an argumentative essay EXCEPT:",
      "choice": [
        "Statistics,",
        "Your opinion,",
        "Questions",
        "Shock Statements"
      ],
      "answer": 1,
      "explanation": "",
      "keywords": []
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "question": "The supporting details in the essay are:",
      "choice": [
        "restating the question,",
        "thesis statements",
        "summarizing",
        "evidence"
      ],
      "answer": 3,
      "explanation": "",
      "keywords": []
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "question": "This type of essay illustrates the similarities and differences between two subjects:",
      "choice": ["Compare and contrast", "T-charts", "Narrative", "Persuasive"],
      "answer": 0,
      "explanation": "",
      "keywords": []
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "question": "In this step of the writing process, you create a graphic organizer.",
      "choice": ["Writing", "Publishing", "Editing", "Prewriting"],
      "answer": 3,
      "explanation": "",
      "keywords": []
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "question": "This is the final step of the writing process.",
      "choice": ["Publishing", "Writing", "Revising", "Editing"],
      "answer": 0,
      "explanation": "",
      "keywords": []
    }
  ]
}
